<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="atom.xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://LearnToHomeLab.github.io/LearnToHomeLabDocumentation/blog</id>
    <title>Learn To HomeLab Blog</title>
    <updated>2025-10-30T20:03:07.414Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://LearnToHomeLab.github.io/LearnToHomeLabDocumentation/blog"/>
    <subtitle>Learn To HomeLab Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://LearnToHomeLab.github.io/LearnToHomeLabDocumentation/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Site!]]></title>
        <id>https://LearnToHomeLab.github.io/LearnToHomeLabDocumentation/blog/welcome</id>
        <link href="https://LearnToHomeLab.github.io/LearnToHomeLabDocumentation/blog/welcome"/>
        <updated>2025-10-30T20:03:07.414Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the new site]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 class="anchor anchorTargetStickyNavbar_Vzrq" id="welcome-to-the-new-site">Welcome to the new site<a href="https://learntohomelab.github.io/LearnToHomeLabDocumentation/blog/welcome#welcome-to-the-new-site" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Welcome to the new site" title="Direct link to Welcome to the new site" translate="no">​</a></h2>
<p>Hey guys, Abe here!</p>
<p>I just wanted to be the first person to welcome you to the latest revision of the website.</p>
<p>We personally knew that the old website just didn't meet our standards, it was also more limiting in the capabilities we could output with it. The new site uses a much more robust backend that will allow us to introduce more features into our content and tutorials.</p>
<p>As you can see, the website also has a blog section now, we will be using this for future content you will hopefully be seeing on the channel before the end of 2025.</p>
<p>Key Advantages:</p>
<ol>
<li class="">The website supports .mdx.</li>
<li class="">We now have a blog section.</li>
<li class="">The site allows for JavaScript integration, making our documentation process more fluid.</li>
<li class="">We now have more control over the websites look.</li>
<li class="">We changed how images are shown, now they are a pop up instead of opening in a new tab.</li>
<li class="">At the end of one tutorial, you can automatically go to the next.</li>
<li class="">The site now has a better footer than can be observed on all pages of the site.</li>
<li class="">We have integrated links into the footer for our other projects (More coming soon!).</li>
<li class="">We now have a better built-in search bar.</li>
<li class="">Our site directly connects to our Github, so you can find resources more easily as we release them.</li>
</ol>
<p>The LTH team wants you to know that we are all very appreciative for every single one of you. Without the community, we would be unable to make these dreams come true.</p>
<p>“Empowering you with knowledge, building a stronger community, and fostering collaboration.”</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Abe P.</name>
            <uri>https://www.linkedin.com/in/abrampeterson/</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="LTH_News" term="LTH_News"/>
    </entry>
</feed>